The spines that this mask
uses can pierce a human brain.
However, they don't yet have the
strength to probe our immortal brains.
The solution is finding more power.
Ooh, what's that now?
The mortals call it the Red Stone of Asia.
Its power is of a particular
interest for our kind.
This little stone can refract
light at least a billion times.
The end result is light of
incredible purity and strength.
This amplified light holds power untold.
But this one won't do.
This little red pebble isn't large enough.
We need more capacity and strength in it.
To complete our mask, we need a red
stone that is large and utterly flawless.
We need a super Asia.
Once we have that,
we will conquer the sun and then become
the final perfect step in evolution.
The masks were invented by the oldest
pillar man among them, and his name is Kars.
Cars ACDC and Mama cross the Atlantic in
their search for a suitable Super Asia.
There you are, Susie Q.
Signora, here, just like you wanted.
Thank you.
You see this?
What I have in my hand here is a
natural, perfectly flawless stone.
A Super Asia. Whoa!
You've been carrying the
red stone of Asia around?
The warriors of Harmon were
wiped out by the Pillar Men.
This stone narrowly avoided being taken,
and now I have been given
the honor to be its guardian.
Caesar, I know exactly how you feel.
The stone masks not only
killed our grandfathers,
but they took the lives of
countless others as well.
And now we've met its creator, Kars.
Just break it!
Yeah, crush the damn thing.
Smash it to pieces and
they'll cry like babies.
No, I can't do that. Why?
What's stopping you?
Legend says the Pillamen can't be defeated
unless the stone is somehow a part
of the process. What? That's crazy.
Why would that be?
I don't know.
But I will perform my duty
as guardian as best I can.
Jojo, Caesar, I'm afraid it's
necessary for a final examination.
What?
A final exam?
Caesar, take on Machina and defeat him.
Jojo, you have the same
assignment but with logs.
Are you two ready?
Thank you.
Are you ready, Caesar?
I was born ready!
It's almost dawn.
It's always darkest then.
Now, where could I
expect Logs to be hiding?
Stay sharp, Joseph. Eyes open.
You've got a score to settle with him.
Huh?
Is that Instructor Logs?
Horrible! Unnatural!
Instructor Logs!
He's dead!
Easy Pass!
So you came to Venice!
Came here to this island!
To think that the woman guarding the stone
is merely an island or two over that way.
His lungs were pulled out.
Lungs are vital for Harmon users.
It had to have been a
kick of incredible power.
The tyrant logs.
You yelled at me for three weeks.
You were relentless
with your instructions.
To be honest, I hated you.
I was sure that this would be my chance to
get you back for everything you did to me
you'll have to watch me from where you are
now instructor see what
i've learned from you
hey acedisi i know it's
six days early but i'll
take it now that antidote
in your nose ring is mine
out of my way boy i don't
have the time to deal
with you you don't have
the time what do you
mean you have a lot more
time than i do that was
pretty sharp you may have
a little more to offer
but when someone looks at me with
an obvious challenge like that one?
They are asking for their death.
I'll tell you this one
more time. Back away.
You know that with one touch of my hand,
you'll soon be missing half of your body.
Just try to move me.
Ooh.
What's this now? Oh, look.
I'm still here.
I only move for important
things, like dog poo in my path.
Using his hamon, he's able to break
right through the flesh of my hand.
He's learned a great deal of control
in a very short period of time.
However...
You've developed new skills.
I have to say I'm rather surprised.
But you're still far from
ready to fight someone like me!
I've met and devoured countless Hamon
users like you thousands of years ago!
If I twist your finger completely off,
you'll never use it for Hamon ever again!
Like this!
Oh, you finally noticed!
Your arm is wrapped up in
a loop of fine silk thread.
It's soaked in vegetable oil, so it
really conducts Hamon quite well.
I admit I was aiming for your neck,
but you didn't give me the chance.
How could a mortal have done this to me?
But but that's.
Actually a little morbid for my taste,
but still first blood goes
to me and my instructor. Ah!
2,500 years ago in China,
a man wrote The Art of War.
He said this, victory is decided
before the battle is fought.
That means if you plan to win,
you need to lay out strategies
while your opponent is unaware.
It's true that I skipped school a lot,
But Granny Iran made darn
sure I studied my history.
So while you may have a lot
of years under your belt,
you didn't leave any room
in your head for strategy.
Take that!
How dare you?
Oh, are you angry?
Are you upset that I
disintegrated your widow arm?
Well, then, get upset!
I'm far more furious than you!
Because of that little ring you
saw fit to put inside my neck,
I haven't slept right for weeks!
Huh?
I just can't take it!
No! No!
What the hell is this?
He's bawling his eyes out, and I
thought he'd go on a bloody rampage.
This is more than weird.
This is embarrassing.
He's throwing a tantrum
like some three-year-old.
My poor arm!
Some things are creepier
than mindless anger.
I should finish him off quickly.
I feel better now.
Sometimes my emotions overwhelm me.
And when I'm about to lose it,
I try to calm myself down by
venting with a crying jag.
Earlier you referred
to Sun Tzu, didn't you?
I knew him personally.
Long ago, I journeyed to China to study.
To fight us to delude.
All war is deception.
One tries to make their
enemies angry in order
to lure them into
committing costly mistakes.
That is precisely what you're
planning on, am I right?
Well, it's not going to work.
But I must say, Jojo, I really
am shocked at your improvement.
I admire your harm-on ability.
I've been longing for a worthy opponent.
What the hell?
What are you doing?
Well, it is a bit thin at the moment,
but it'll grow thicker
with the passage of time.
He's too much.
Just a minute ago, he was crying.
Oh, Jojo.
Did I just frighten you there?
Come on, admit it.
You're frightened a lot, aren't you?
I can't read him.
I've always been able to read my opponents
and then use their own
feelings against them.
But this guy's personality is beyond me.
Am I the one who's being read here?
What's happening to Log's body?
That burns!
His body, it's boiling.
What's going on?
An animal's core temperature
will increase when
its fighting disease are
greatly exerting itself.
I can raise my blood up to 500
degrees and then shoot it out at will.
At the same time, I took off his arm.
I also sent in some of my
boiling blood to show you.
With his divine sandstorm,
Wamu can control the wind.
My domain is that of heat.
I control the inferno.
I'll grant that your power to destroy
a defenseless, dead body is amazing.
But I can also see that the reason
you did it was to try and scare me!
Now try a clack of volley!
My hormone isn't like it was a month ago!
I really did frighten you.
You see, Jojo,
your uncontrolled emotions caused you
to attack me recklessly and too soon.
My veins will inject boiling
blood into your skull
and then turn your brain
into a nice red stew.
This is the reason that I am
called the Burning King! Gah!
Gah!
Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah!
SEASUR, TAKE THIS!
ABOLUNCHE!
SEASUR, STOP!
Hold your attack!
If we continue this contest,
one or both of us will die.
And much as my ego doesn't want
to admit it, I'd be the loser.
For nearly ten years more than
you, I've been in preparation here.
But today, your hormone
attack was so focused,
you were able to burn
the hair off of my arm.
What else can I do after
being shamed like this?
You have passed your final
exam with flying colors.
You should feel a sense of pride for this.
Or are you more interested in how your
good-for-nothing friend is doing in his exam,
Caesar?
The only reason I had
the power I did in this
training is that I wanted
to match Jojo's talents.
In the end, we're both going to survive
the trials being presented to us.
I can't deny it.
Jojo seems lazy and impudent.
But deep down, he's
worth having as a friend.
You're not so good at making
friends for yourself, are you?
But when you do, it's true love, isn't it?
Look there!
It's in easy!
Hmm.
And there's another of those
clever dodges of yours.
All right.
The mask gave me some
protection that time, but...
Ah, damn him and his blood!
Man, oh man,
I finally have the chance for these sexy
lips to come out from
under that rotten mask.
And the first thing you do,
you bastard, is burn them off!
Jojo, hmm, let's see.
On the surface you make witty banter.
But inside your head you're making
all sorts of plans, aren't you?
You went pale, Jojo Did I hit the mark?
Was I anywhere close to the bullseye?
My next plan...
Right, yes, I'll use the string.
I'll act like I'm dodging
to get away from him,
but all the time I'll be running a string
along these spikes with each move I make.
I can't let him catch on.
Once he steps inside the string,
I'll wrap him up in it, then use
my hormone to finish him off.
That laugh means trouble.
Could he be reading my plan?
My intentions?
No, it's impossible.
Here is the Burning King's prison!
How long can you possibly keep
avoiding my attacks, Jojo?
So I guess you finally noticed.
Now what possible reason
would my hat be shrieking?
You appear to be caught in my well.
My hat is made of 100 % wool.
It conducts harmon very well.
And...
You're smiling again.
I don't like it.
What are you laughing about this time?
The next words from your mouth are,
I'm going to knock that
smirk right off of your face.
Watch.
I'm going to knock that
smirk right off your face!
Wait a second, you can't do that!
That's my trick!
You said you had a web?
Look around, I am the one with the web.
I knew exactly what you had in mind with
your little plan even before you did.
So, Jojo, what was that
phrase you said earlier?
Something like victory is decided before
the battle is fought, was that what it was?
How incredibly true were
the words you spoke.
But my plans were the ones to go deeper.
My plans were the ones to decide victory.
It looks like my veins have created
some little holes on your body.
So now I'll fill every one of them
with a generous portion of my boiling,
burning blood.
You'll look like a lovely birthday
cake covered in candles flickering?
with their merry little red flames.
He's on the knife's edge.
He's not going to make it. Caesar!
Judging from what I can see, we have
to assume that Logs has been killed.
If Jojo is not the one to survive, we will
be the ones ACDC will come after next.
Jojo is too far away for us
to be able to help him now.
I know it's painful,
but right now we have to think about
protecting Lisa Lisa and the Red Stone.
So come, let's make our preparations.
Jojo...
Let me hear your screams as you twitch
and writhe in despair and agony,
knowing that you lost today, Jojo!
Are you really laughing as I'm about
to deal you an excruciating death?
Have you been driven
completely insane by the fear?
Well, let's see here.
You'll notice my arms are
folded and my eyes are closed,
so this laugh would be one of victory.
ACDC,
you're the loser here today
because for the last 2,000 years,
you have been asleep at the wheel.
I lost?
What do you mean by that? Oh, really?
You don't get it?
You can't read me as clearly
as you thought you could.
Let me help you understand just
how badly you've underestimated me.
You said that your plans went deep.
Well, they didn't go
nearly as deep as mine.
While you were snoozing for the past
2,000 years, humans have progressed.
During the 18th and 19th centuries,
leisure de main, or sleight of hand, became
a very popular form of entertainment.
I'm a really big fan of it myself.
Illusion is my thing!
But I cut all those strings!
I cut them!
It can't be!
I'd say the rope magic works.
I laid my trap carefully
so that even if the string
was cut it would still
function a simple trick.
What you're going to say
next is my veins will move
faster than your pathetic
hormone can possibly go now!.
My veins will move faster than your
pathetic hormone could possibly go.
Now feel the beat of
my hormone overdrive?.
I can't.
You're only a human.
I am the evolved one.
The highest life form!
I will not be beaten!
Know that you pushed me too far!
ACDC's body is shooting
some kind of strange energy.
That must come from living for millennia.
Die already.
Die with the power of life you stole
from thousands of innocent human beings.
My instructor, I thank
you for torturing me.
Mille Crazy to you, Lord.
When we defeated San Viento in the
well, his entire body turned into stone.
But even ACDC's bones
were completely destroyed.
Why is he so different?
Well, maybe it's because my harmon is
so much stronger than it was before.
Well, he's dead now, and I have one of
the antidotes I've been chasing down.
Oh, man, this reminds me of snot.
Hopefully it's just because it's stripping
from a ring that came out of his nose.
But I need to knock it back.
Yes, I do think it worked.
The ring around my windpipe is
gone and I can breathe free again.
So then, I'll go see Lisa-Lisa and Caesar.
I think maybe I was using my
head too much in that fight.
My shoulders are really kind of stiff.
I'll be the roundabout.
The words will make you out and out.
I'll spend the day your way.
Call it morning driving through the sun.
I'm in and out the valley.
The music dance and sing.
They make the children really ring.
I spend the day your way.
Cold in morning driving through the sun.
And in and out the valley.
And out around the lake.
Mountains come out of the sky.
I understand, girl.
One mile over, we'll be
there and we'll see you.
Ten, two summers, we'll
be there laughing too.
Twenty, forty, four mile
over, we'll see you.
I'll be there with you.
I think the white one is pretty.
We'll wait for that until we cross.
But I really like the
lovely design on this one.
I'll eradicate every one of them.
Oh, which do I choose?
Damn it all!
I just can't hit her!